Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
Rest assured.
اطمئن، لا تشغل بالك.
He won't be going anywhere anytime soon.
لن يذهب إلى أي مكان في أي وقت قريب.
You go first.
ابدأ أنت أولاً.
Li Xiang and I will cover your retreat.
سأقوم أنا ولي شيانغ بتغطية فترة استجمامكم.
Xie Xinxu.
شيه شينكسو.
That shot counts as your apology.
تُعتبر تلك اللقطة بمثابة اعتذار منك.
You screw me over again,
لقد خذلتني مرة أخرى،
I’ll blow your head off.
سأفجر رأسك.
I wasn't apologizing.
لم أكن أعتذر.
You got captured
لقد تم القبض عليك
because you were weak.
لأنك كنت ضعيفاً.
♪You smell like something strange♪
رائحتك غريبة!
♪Like wood♪
♪مثل الخشب♪
♪Like wine♪
♪مثل النبيذ♪
♪Like the fading rain♪
♪مثل المطر المتلاشي♪
♪It's not a problem I can fix♪
♪ليست مشكلة أستطيع حلها♪
♪Maybe I'm just meant to be your toy…♪
♪ربما أنا مجرد لعبة بين يديكِ…♪
You drive well.
أنت تقود بشكل جيد.
What kind of amateur shot was that?
ما نوع هذه اللقطة الهاوية؟
How did you even pass your driving test?
كيف اجتزت اختبار القيادة أصلاً؟
I'll handle the shooting.
سأتولى أمر إطلاق النار.
♪I keep telling myself, to find a way out♪
أظل أقول لنفسي، أن أجد مخرجاً.
♪But every time I try it, you bring me go of myself♪
♪لكن في كل مرة أحاول فيها ذلك، تجعلني أفقد نفسي♪
♪Your voice's all my ears so sweet, sweet♪
صوتكِ يملأ أذني، يا له من صوتٍ عذبٍ وعذب!
♪Guess I'll stay at where your love is all around♪
♪أظن أنني سأبقى حيث يحيط بي حبك من كل جانب♪
Ready?
مستعد؟
What?
ماذا؟
The wind's too loud. I couldn't hear you.
الرياح شديدة للغاية. لم أستطع سماعك.
Can you explain it first before you act next time?
هل يمكنك شرح الأمر أولاً قبل أن تتصرف في المرة القادمة؟
What did you say?
ماذا قلت؟
The wind's too loud. I couldn't hear you.
الرياح شديدة للغاية. لم أستطع سماعك.
We're heading to Sunset Forest.
سنتوجه إلى غابة الغروب.
According to Max's intel,
بحسب معلومات ماكس الاستخباراتية،
the fragment should be there.
يجب أن يكون الجزء موجوداً.
Shouldn't we go to the hospital first?
ألا ينبغي أن نذهب إلى المستشفى أولاً؟
It's fine.
لا بأس.
The bullet just grazed me.
أصابتني الرصاصة إصابة طفيفة.
I can still hold on.
ما زلت أستطيع الصمود.
If we don't go now,
إذا لم نذهب الآن،
Max will tighten security even more.
سيعمل ماكس على تشديد الإجراءات الأمنية بشكل أكبر.
Starting navigation to Sunset Forest.
بدء الملاحة إلى غابة الغروب.
Stop the car.
أوقف السيارة.
There's something wrong with the fog in this forest.
هناك شيء خاطئ في الضباب في هذه الغابة.
Hold at the intersection.
توقف عند التقاطع.
We'll go in after the fog clears.
سندخل بعد أن ينقشع الضباب.
Why am I so sleepy?
لماذا أشعر بالنعاس الشديد؟
Wasn't I supposed to be in Sunset Forest?
ألم يكن من المفترض أن أكون في غابة الغروب؟
Where am I?
أين أنا؟
Xie Xinxu.
شيه شينكسو.
Good morning, everyone.
صباح الخير جميعاً.
Today is November 31st, 2020.
اليوم هو 31 نوفمبر 2020.
On this day in history,
في مثل هذا اليوم من التاريخ،
the well known writer Lin Yu
الكاتب المعروف لين يو
published his first full length novel, Silence.
نشر روايته الأولى كاملة الطول، بعنوان "الصمت".
The year 2020?
عام 2020؟
Did I travel back five years?
هل سافرت بالزمن خمس سنوات إلى الوراء؟
Xie Xinxu.
شيه شينكسو.
If you see my girlfriend again,
إذا رأيت حبيبتي مرة أخرى،
stay away from her. Got it?
ابتعد عنها. فهمت؟
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Let's talk this out.
دعنا نتحدث في هذا الأمر.
Who are you, stepping in like this for him?
من أنت حتى تتدخل هكذا من أجله؟
He's my husband.
هو زوجي.
So you're being kept by a pretty lady.
إذن أنت تعيش مع سيدة جميلة.
Watch your mouth. You spread rumors way too easily.
انتبه لكلامك. أنت تنشر الشائعات بسهولة بالغة.
Leave. Now.
ارحل. الآن.
Or I'll call the police.
وإلا سأتصل بالشرطة.
Search her. Take her phone.
فتشها. خذ هاتفها.
♪I am lost in the dizzy pull of your fierce attraction♪
♪أنا تائه في سحر جاذبيتك القوية التي تُدوّخني♪
♪So devoted that I would let this obsession last until the end of my life♪
♪مخلصٌ لدرجة أنني سأدع هذا الهوس يستمر حتى نهاية حياتي♪
♪Will your love ever burn as fiercely as mine?♪
هل سيشتعل حبك يوماً ما بنفس شدة حبي؟
You're going to kill them.
سوف تقتلهم.
Xie Xinxu.
شيه شينكسو.
Who are you?
من أنت؟
Why would you say
لماذا تقول ذلك؟
we're in that kind of relationship?
هل نحن في علاقة من هذا النوع؟
Am I the only one who went back in time?
هل أنا الوحيد الذي عاد بالزمن إلى الوراء؟
The person in front of me
الشخص الذي أمامي
is Xie Xinxu from five years ago, before he ever met me.
هذا هو شي شينشو من خمس سنوات مضت، قبل أن يقابلني.
I had a dream that foretold the future.
حلمت حلماً تنبأ بالمستقبل.
In that dream,
في ذلك الحلم،
I was your wife.
كنت زوجتك.
In the future.
في المستقبل.
Get off.
ترجل.
What are you still trying to do?
ما الذي ما زلت تحاول فعله؟
Why are you burning up?
لماذا تشعر بالحرارة الشديدة؟
You've got a fever.
أنت مصاب بالحمى.
(Watch on www.kissasia.co, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
(شاهد على www.kissasia.co، .be، .org، .net، .id، .xyz)
We're going to the hospital.
سنذهب إلى المستشفى.
If I went back in time,
لو عدت بالزمن إلى الوراء،
how would I get back to my own time?
كيف سأعود إلى زمني الأصلي؟
That's an intense presence.
هذا حضور قوي.
If you don't mind,
إن لم يكن لديك مانع،
could you come in and explain?
هل يمكنك الدخول وشرح الأمر؟
What exactly happened to my son?
ما الذي حدث بالضبط لابني؟
Did Xu get into a fight outside?
هل دخل شو في شجار بالخارج؟
No.
لا.
He just tripped outside by accident.
لقد تعثر بالخارج عن طريق الخطأ.
I was a bit worried,
كنت قلقاً بعض الشيء،
so I walked him back.
لذلك رافقته إلى الخلف.
Judging by how you're dressed,
بالنظر إلى طريقة لباسك،
you don't look like his classmate.
أنت لا تشبه زميله في الصف.
How old are you?
كم عمرك؟
I'm twenty three.
عمري ثلاثة وعشرون عاماً.
We're very grateful you brought Xu home today.
نحن ممتنون للغاية لأنك أحضرت شو إلى المنزل اليوم.
But
لكن
he's only just started college.
لقد بدأ دراسته الجامعية للتو.
You're already working in society.
أنت تعمل بالفعل في المجتمع.
So considering all aspects,
لذا، مع الأخذ في الاعتبار جميع الجوانب،
we don't think it's appropriate for you to be friends.
لا نعتقد أنه من المناسب أن تكونا صديقين.
I think it's perfectly fine.
أعتقد أن الأمر على ما يرام تماماً.
And
و
I'm pursuing her right now.
أنا ألاحقها الآن.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Why did you say you were pursuing me?
لماذا قلت إنك كنت تلاحقني؟
My parents are rigid and old fashioned.
والداي متشددان وقديمان في التفكير.
They'd worry you might toy with my feelings.
سيقلقون من أنك قد تتلاعب بمشاعري.
They'd warn you, keep an eye on you,
سيحذرونك، ويراقبونك،
and make sure you stay away from me.
وتأكد من ابتعادك عني.
You can only see each other three times a week.
لا يمكنكما رؤية بعضكما البعض إلا ثلاث مرات في الأسبوع.
You must be home by nine at the latest.
يجب أن تكون في المنزل بحلول الساعة التاسعة كحد أقصى.
And
و
cannot affect his studies.
لا يمكن أن يؤثر ذلك على دراسته.
This is the bottom line.
هذا هو جوهر الموضوع.
If you can't follow these rules,
إذا لم تتمكن من اتباع هذه القواعد،
we will oppose any further contact.
سنعارض أي اتصال آخر.
That's fine with me.
لا بأس بذلك بالنسبة لي.
Fetch the camera.
أحضر الكاميرا.
The school
المدرسة
gave every Provincial Outstanding Teacher
منح جائزة المعلم المتميز على مستوى المقاطعة لكل معلم
a camera as a reward.
كاميرا كمكافأة.
Since we have the chance,
بما أن لدينا الفرصة،
I'll test it to see if it's working properly.
سأختبره لأرى ما إذا كان يعمل بشكل صحيح.
Can I have a look?
هل يمكنني إلقاء نظرة؟
What a nice vintage camera.
يا لها من كاميرا عتيقة رائعة.
I've wanted one for a long time.
كنت أرغب في الحصول على واحدة منذ فترة طويلة.
This is this year's new model.
هذا هو الطراز الجديد لهذا العام.
I'm saying this design has a real vintage feel.
أقول إن هذا التصميم يتمتع بطابع كلاسيكي حقيقي.
And its burst mode is pretty powerful too.
ووضع الاندفاع فيه قوي جدًا أيضًا.
How do you use burst mode?
كيف تستخدم وضع التصوير المتتابع؟
Madam, you're very photogenic.
سيدتي، أنتِ جميلة جداً في الصور.
You look exactly the same in person.
تبدو تمامًا كما أنت في الواقع.
Sir,
سيد،
if your bangs were a bit longer,
لو كانت غرتك أطول قليلاً،
you'd look just like a Korean oppa.
ستبدو تماماً مثل أوبا كوري.
Really?
حقًا؟
And this one!
وهذا واحد أيضاً!
Madam's smile looks great here.
ابتسامة السيدة تبدو رائعة هنا.
How about
ماذا عن
we take a couple more?
هل نأخذ اثنين آخرين؟
The frame's full of people.
الإطار مليء بالناس.
You can't really tell if the color is vivid enough.
لا يمكنك حقًا معرفة ما إذا كان اللون زاهيًا بما فيه الكفاية.
Noisy.
صاخب.
You're driving me crazy.
أنت تُجنّنني.
I'll go check on him.
سأذهب لأطمئن عليه.
Don't lock the door.
لا تغلق الباب.
Your fever's gotten worse.
لقد ازدادت حرارتك سوءاً.
Get up.
استيقظ.
Come on.
تعال.
You look like you're about to go berserk.
تبدو وكأنك على وشك أن تفقد أعصابك.
I can help you.
أستطيع مساعدتك.
I don't know what you're talking about.
لا أعرف عما تتحدث.
Leave.
يترك.
But if you go berserk, you will hurt someone.
لكن إذا فقدت أعصابك، فسوف تؤذي شخصاً ما.
Don't you remember those troublemakers?
ألا تتذكر هؤلاء المشاغبين؟
What if you hurt your parents?
ماذا لو آذيت والديك؟
Trust me just once.
ثق بي ولو لمرة واحدة.
I can't do anything bad to you anyway.
لا أستطيع أن أفعل لك أي شيء سيء على أي حال.
Then what are you going to do...
إذن ماذا ستفعل...
to help me?
هل يمكنك مساعدتي؟
Do you feel any better now?
هل تشعر بتحسن الآن؟
Try to relax.
حاول الاسترخاء.
You're holding too tight.
أنت تتمسك بقوة شديدة.
That hurts.
هذا مؤلم.
It hurts.
إنه مؤلم.
You…
أنت…
You crossed a line.
لقد تجاوزت الحدود.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Looks like I'll have to pull out the big move.
يبدو أنني سأضطر إلى القيام بالانتقال الكبير.
Why are your lips swollen?
لماذا شفتاك منتفختان؟
Did you two
هل فعلتما ذلك؟
just now
الآن
eat spicy snacks?
تناول وجبات خفيفة حارة؟
Have this instead.
تناول هذا بدلاً من ذلك.
Don't eat those junk snacks.
لا تأكل تلك الوجبات الخفيفة غير الصحية.
Um...
واحد...
It's already 8:30 PM. Keep an eye on the time.
الساعة الآن الثامنة والنصف مساءً. انتبه للوقت.
Take it.
خذها.
♪You smell like something strange♪
رائحتك غريبة!
♪Like wood♪
♪مثل الخشب♪
♪Like wine♪
♪مثل النبيذ♪
♪Like the fading rain♪
♪مثل المطر المتلاشي♪
♪It's not a problem I can fix♪
♪ليست مشكلة أستطيع حلها♪
♪Maybe I'm just meant to be your toy♪
♪ربما أنا مجرد لعبة بالنسبة لك♪